What am I doing on a Sunday night at 10 p.m.?
You may be wondering, or you may not be wondering, but I'm gonna tell you.
I am getting ready for bed because I'm gonna wake up at 5 a.m. tomorrow morning.
The fact that it's still completely pitch black outside and no sign of the sun rising anytime soon really makes me want to just go back to bed.
Well, many things make me want to go back to bed.
Oh, I'm so dramatic.
I don't want to complain about this, but like I actually really don't want to get up right
now.
It feels so lonely.
No one's up, but it is so nice that I have like at least the lights from the city.
Whoa, I, oh my gosh, I just saw them turn on all the office.
All of these lights just lit up at once.
Wow, do you think that guy runs every morning?
I usually wake up so excited for breakfast.
Like it's kind of maybe a bit concerning and I'm like not hungry at all.
If I don't get out of my apartment right now, I am about to get back into bed.
I can feel the internal conflict I'm having.
I never really hear the birds here, honestly, ever.
But they're so loud this morning.
I don't know if it's because I'm hearing less traffic noise.
That's why it's just more prominent.
Good morning to you all.
I come to you from the mall?
Food court?
Oh, we have an early riser.
What a king.
Thank god for my Dunkin'.
If I didn't have this this morning, where would be the light?
I was just thinking about how I'm getting Dunkin' all morning.
I just knew in my head that's what I was gonna do.
I got an iced caramel latte, skim milk, pump of caramel swirl, and a pump of French vanilla.
Yes, this is a lot of sugar.
All right, I'm treating myself for, you know, this tragedy of a morning.
This is usually my people watching spot.
Not a lot of people to watch this morning though.
I do have a confession guys.
I sat on my couch this morning.
Never doing that again because I did fall asleep for 20 minutes.
So I'm not perfect.
Okay I had to be honest.
Like I had to be honest.
That's what happened.
Learned my lesson there.
Couch is a no-go for me.
Since I'm up this early I might as well just like get started on work.
I also should have gotten ready more because like why am I wearing my sweatpants that I wore to bed.
The issue is that I also went to bed late.
I went to bed at, I think I fell asleep at like 11:30, which in theory is not that late.
That's like the time I usually go to bed, but I need to be adjusting.
I need to be going to bed at like 9 p.m. if I'm going to be waking up at 5.
So I'm a little fearful about my day ahead.
Anyways, I'm gonna do some work.
I might as well.
I'm up and I have a lot to do.
So oh, we have another morning man or morning
king.
It is currently 3 p.m. Somehow I had it in me to work out.
I actually don't have it in me, but this was pre-scheduled, so I can't really cancel.
I just had my second coffee of the day.
I kind of feel numb a little bit, like I'm so tired that I feel like I pushed past it.
So I'm doing fine now.
We'll see how I am later.
Head comes down in three.
Head comes.
It was the roomie's birthday, Olivia.
We celebrated later that night with some drinks.
I think it was around like 10:30.
Hey guys, so I had a really fun night.
Maybe too fun because now it is 12:5 a.m. I am worried.
Okay, I have this sense of impending doom upon me because I was supposed to get to bed early and here we are.
So I'm irresponsible.
Basically I'm irresponsible and this is all my fault.
You already know we have to do it all over again tomorrow morning and I'm feeling concerned.
Today felt so long.
It felt like three days combined into one.
Definitely not excited to wake up at five tomorrow.
It's gonna like actually suck.
You will see me in a bad mood in probably a second.
Love you.
Good morning.
I being so vulnerable posting myself right when I wake up because wow, I never want to see what I look like the second that I wake up
ever again.
It's 5.
Can you see this?
I think I absolutely have to get out of my apartment right now because otherwise I am going to get back into.
Bed and fall asleep.
Or I'm going to sit on the couch and fall asleep.
I also am like, should I just go to the gym and like get my workout out of the way?
I
am wearing the same hoodie that I wore to bed.
Yes, you are not seeing things.
This week I had a lot of oatmeal, particularly because it was so easy and light for me before the gym.
This was me seriously contemplating sitting on the couch for just a couple minutes, but we all know how that would have turned out, so I went to
the gym.
I made it in time to see the sunrise, which was so beautiful.
It really like lifted my spirits.
Honestly, I think this is probably the best way I could have started the morning.
Watching the sunrise while working out somehow, um, it really motivated me, and I'm surprised that I'm not exhausted.
I thought either after I would be super exhausted or have a lot of energy, and luckily it's the latter for me, so it's always so rewarding after.
It's also only 7:05 a.m. Usually at this point, I'm still sleeping in my bed, and I've already done so much today.
Nothing brings me more joy than this smoothie.
You guys know it's my go-to.
I'll probably eat this for the next six months until I absolutely hate it.
I just got ready.
It's 8:30 a.m. Drinking my smoothie.
I just switched up a little bit today because I ran out of frozen strawberries.
I just feel so happy.
I feel like these mornings are the best way to set your day up.
I never have once regretted like waking up early to go to the gym.
Never in my life.
Do I always dread it?
Yes.
I'm gonna grab my stuff, go to the coffee shop to work, because we all know I'm 20 times more productive when I'm out.
Also, look at those flowers.
I feel a lot more productive and just better when I get ready in the morning, even if it's just like two seconds of me putting on some
concealer and sunscreen.
It makes me feel like I had a little bit of a routine.
To conclude my morning routine, I grabbed my brick.
This has been my new favorite thing.
It's a physical device that basically locks me out of my phone and my social media, which has immensely helped my productivity.
I can't even put into words how much it's helped me.
As sad as it is that I kind of needed it, it was something that I'd considered getting for a while, you guys know.
It's currently 10 a.m., and guys, I kind of, okay, I'm kind of loving it now.
I feel like I've lived a full day already.
I feel like I've had a full afternoon of work, and it's not even noon yet.
I kind of feel a little bit less stressed.
Like I have way more time than I usually do, obviously.
And I feel like I have way more time to be productive, and I'm not like cramming things in.
By the way, last night, I forgot to tell you guys, I woke up five different times between the span of 1 a.m. and 4 a.m. in a
sheer panic to look at the time on my phone.
I must have been panicking that my alarm wouldn't go off or something.
Like, what's the psychology there?
Does anybody know why?
Why I did that, or am I just, um, insane?
Maybe.
Anyways, I'm just working right now.
I'm editing this video that you're watching, and then two videos for Instagram reels.
I'm actually dying.
Why was I filming that so far away?
Like, it looked like I was two miles away from the camera.
Oh no, here we go.
I did forget.
Forgot I did this.
I grabbed another coffee.
Yeah, I definitely needed it this day because I just was on my laptop.
I did switch locations, but it finally hit me.
Now I'm tired.
It's official.
I'm tired.
Um, my head hurts.
I'm being such a wimp, but like four to five hours of sleep a night for me, it's just not what I'm used to.
I don't know if I take a nap or if I just like ride it out.
I might just ride it out till tonight, but it's 1 p.m., and I've already gotten so much done, which is like the best feeling in the world.
So honestly, I don't really care that I'm exhausted.
At least I'm getting stuff done.
Hey guys, I'm at a grand dinner.
It is 7:30 p.m. Wish me luck.
I have to wake up at 5 a.m. tomorrow.
Just doing it to herself.
Hey guys, I'm on my way home from the Event it went great.
Although all I can think about is sleeping in my bed immediately.
I'm very exhausted, even though I don't look like it.
I like, I'm barely hanging on by a thread at this point.
So, so I did get a new mug.
Um, why does it look like it wants to punch me?
I've never been so happy to be in my bed.
I'm drinking my chamomile tea and then gonna go straight to bed.
Problem is, it's already 11:30.
To be fair, you know, I had an event tonight that I did have to go to, and there are people who have to wake up at 5
every day.
I think I would enjoy this if I was getting to bed earlier.
Good night, guys.
Guys, I don't know what happened, but somehow, someway, I woke up 10 minutes before my alarm.
I slept so well.
I feel like I'm not actually dreading to- well, I am dreading- I always dread to get out of bed.
Oh, and it's April Fool's Day.
Happy April Fool's.
Happy April Fool's Day to all who celebrate, including myself, although I have nothing planned.
I need to use it to my advantage that I woke up early because I can't let this go to waste.
This is huge for me.
This is huge for the program.
It's so dark out.
Oh my gosh, it's so early.
I kind of really want Duncan, and I also want to just like stay here today and clean because my apartment is sort of accumulating a disaster mess.
I think I figured something out, guys.
Something that helps me in the morning, I've realized.
Very simple, but an ice bath for my face.
I don't actually use a whole ice bath thing.
I mean, especially at 5 a.m. Like, you will not see me doing a full ice bath, but I just take cold water splashed on my face when
I wake up.
And that like seriously just woke me up and revived me.
Clearly, guys, look at this.
I'm kind of adjusting, you know, it's just so quiet.
Like, it's so well.
All right.
As soon as I say that, there's a siren.
I'm sitting on the floor because if I was sitting on the couch, we all know what would happen.
So I'm taking some serious precautions here.
I am going to do my five minute journal.
I forgot that I had this, actually.
I also wish I had a pen, but that is currently missing in action.
So I'm just going to use a Sharpie, and I'm going to do a little prompt because I think gratitude journals and things like that really can like
start your day off right.
As much as I wish that this tea would sustain me, I think I, I think I could use some Dunkin'.
This video is really just an excuse for me to get Dunkin' every day.
It really feels like I'm not chasing the day as much.
I feel like I'm always trying to catch up on things, and I'm like one step behind.
I have so much on my plate.
But this makes me feel like I'm one step ahead of everything, and it kind of just like makes my mind clearer.
I also think waking up early kind of makes me less avoidant because I just have the time to do these things.
And one of the things that I really need to do is my room.
Definitely don't want to be doing this now.
But, you know, I have the time.
It's definitely time for a little bit of a deep clean.
And I have a donation pickup tomorrow.
So I want to just get as much stuff out as I can.
My white noise is on, and I am in bed.
It is 11:15 p.m. I've honestly had such busy days, which has been good, but I'm gonna go to bed right away so that way I can wake
up in a brisk six hours.
Hi.
Good morning, guys.
I have a confession.
I hit snooze.
It's 5:40.
The more you snooze, the more like tired I get.
It like puts me in this like weird cyclical pattern.
So I should probably just stop doing that.
I just love my bed.
There's nothing more than my bed.
Okay, joke is over, let's like get up.
I set out my gym clothes the night before, which
always just makes it a little bit easier for me to go the next day.
Honestly, if it wasn't for you guys holding me accountable, I don't know what today would have looked like because I was feeling so tempted to go back
to bed, but I'm so glad that I didn't.
I think what gets me into trouble is entertaining the debate in my head of, should I get up?
Should I go back to sleep?
That's.
When I, you know, that's when things are going downhill.
I had some oatmeal quick before I went to the gym, gotten a little workout.
This was kind of my little routine, actually.
I went to four or five coffee so I could get some work done.
I was feeling pretty productive though.
It is such a compound effect.
The more you get stuff done, the more personally I'm motivated to continue getting stuff done.
So I dropped off an Ophelia package before I headed to the airport because I was flying back home to Minnesota for
Easter.
I'm at the airport now.
I'm flying back to Minnesota.
People are watching me vlog right now and I'm really insecure about it.
I got my second iced coffee of the day.
It's hitting me now.
I was kind of like on a kick for a while.
I was getting a ton done and one of the reasons that I think I got so much done is because I got the brick which I already
showed you guys earlier in the video but it helps me so much to like not go on my phone.
I think I just reach for it out of habit so much and especially after my video where I did like a social media detox I realized how
much I needed that because it's like a physical device I can't just like turn it off in my settings.
I have to like actually go get it which just makes me more aware so that's been really helpful for me in like my mental state.
I'm also having a little sandwich.
I'm really hoping I can get work done on this flight.
I hope I don't fall asleep but it has been so nice.
I just feel like I've had so much time.
Usually I feel like I'm always scrambling to get things done but this week I've gotten like everything done that I've needed two on my to-do
list.
Hello Minnesota.
I am back.
Most importantly, I'm back in my bed.
I knew I was going to sleep in and I was so excited to finally be able to sleep in after waking up at 5 a.m. for a
few days.
Kind of just like my little reward to myself at the end of the week was sleeping in and then getting Dunkin, obviously.
Could I do a iced latte?
What's the blueberry syrup that you have?
Thank you.
I don't know what I just ordered.
I actually have no idea.
Guys, I'm back to my roots.
I'm in Minnesota.
Roots.
I woke up at 10 this morning.
I wanted to just recap a few thoughts that I have while I drink my Dunkin.
This is also a special treat for myself.
I wanted to try something different so I tried this like blueberry vanilla concoction that I just came up with at the window.
Oh wait, it's good.
The blueberry is kind of like life-changing a little bit.
I'm showing you guys because this is so good.
I got a medium iced latte, three french vanilla, one blueberry shot and skim.
Okay, new order.
I'm feeling very nostalgic right now like what in the 2016 is going on right now with my fur teddy coat.
I always concern myself to not be a morning person.
After this week I realized I can be if I want to be.
I don't think you're just like born with it.
I think it's kind of repeating habits over time.
And towards the end of the week, I saw the benefits that I was getting.
Like I had so much more time in the day to get stuff done.
I felt so much more productive.
I loved just having a little bit of time for myself in the morning before the world started.
So I think if I want to be a morning person, I can.
I don't, we're not talking 5am.
That's a little too early for me.
But like, you know, 7 to get my day started right.
I also really realized this week the significance my morning has on the trajectory of my entire day.
When I wake up at nine and I hit snooze and then I slowly get out of bed, my whole day is worse, honestly.
I'm way less productive.
I feel less motivated because I feel like I already failed in the morning.
And then I have like a half-saved day ahead of me.
It's just not the same as being diligent and following through on like what I said that I was going to do.
It is like a bit like minorly empowering to say like, okay, I'm going to wake up tomorrow at five and I'm going to get
up, not snooze and go to the gym and Following through on that not only gives me like more confidence in myself, because I feel like I can
trust myself more, but it also really shapes the rest of my day and just like motivates me to get more done.
And I felt like it was kind of a compound effect, and I know a lot of people do it and like don't have a choice because of
their job.
So um, thanks for joining me.
As someone who is not really a morning person, I feel like I'm shifting a bit, so we'll see.
Anyways, love you guys and see you in my next video.
Bye!